Megafloat Japan and Megafloat
West USA are presently...
...300 kilometers east of Amami
Ooshima, heading northeast.
We have liberated Guam and Okinawa
and are getting closer
to the Japanese mainland.
It's finally time for the mainland battle!
We will take back Japan, our home!
Our target is the capital, Tokyo.
Episode 9
Academy Festa -First Live-
On Wednesdays and Fridays, the beef bowls
at the cafeteria have less sauce.
And on Thursdays, the portions get smaller.
If you overlap the part-timers'
shifts on top of it like this,
you'll see that when Suzuki-san
is working, you get extra sauce,
but when Yamamoto-san is working...
No one cares.
There's other stuff to talk about, right?
Like... you know.
Oh, I figured this would be more interesting.
Hell no!
Sheesh...
Fine.
These are life-sized data figures,
made from my experience and analysis
performing Heart Hybrids...
...during actual combat.
The models use log data from the love room.
They're more than 97 percent accurate.
This is an erogenous zone map,
created using my activities during
the Heart Hybrids and their responses.
Erogenous zones?
I don't know what that means!
I don't know what it means,
but it sounds amazing!
However, they don't always
react in an identical manner.
The way it feels to them is very different
depending on the strength used
and friction coefficients.
Kizuna Hida is a terrifying man!
How much experience does he have?!
The girl's psychological state,
as well as the situation you set,
also change things drastically.
Different individuals react differently,
so there's no general theory.
Each case requires its
own individual decisions.
I'm totally lost!
But there's something more important.
What?!
To understand the feelings of the girl.
What they wish.
What they're seeking.
You need to sense that and
choose the appropriate methods.
He's no amateur!
He's a pro!
Pro Kizuna!
For example...
This is data from Himekawa,
during our attack on the
Super-Category Class Tri-Head.
What the hell are you doing?!
Ataraxia Academy Festa
It's your last chance to relax
before the big battle.
Holiday
Go enjoy yourselves.
You're enjoying yourself
a little too much, idiots.
I've finished presenting my science project
for the first day of the academy festa...
Maybe I'll go check out
what everyone's up to.
Well? Did you find her?
No, no luck.
We can't do our rehearsal like this.
Jeez, where did she go?
Is something wrong?
Kizuna!
Yurishia-san,
don't grab onto him every time you see him!
Oh, did you get hurt?
More importantly,
is there a problem?
Didn't Hayuru just go talk to you?
K-Kizuna-kun was doing a lewd presentation!
I didn't have time to tell him!
It's time for rehearsal,
but there's no sign of Aine.
Of Aine?
We had everyone go look for her,
but nobody can find her.
You try using the PA system?
We sure did.
Made an Ataraxia-wide announcement.
But no luck.
She's either asleep or hiding.
Fine.
I'll go look.
You two start the rehearsal without her.
But how am I supposed to
find her in this crowd?
Hey, it's Mister Kizuna.
The hell are you doing, asshole?
Gertrude!
You're okay now?
I sure am.
No way in hell I'm spending
the festival in bed.
Well, don't push yourself too hard.
Oh, right.
Have you seen Aine?
I tried every food stall out here, but...
I didn't see Aine-san.
Maybe the slut's in the school building?
I see.
Thanks.
Sorry. Have you seen
Aine Chidorigafuchi from Class 2-A?
It's Eros!
It is him!
Run, everyone!
Hey!
Wait!
I don't—
Curse you!
Huh? What's wrong, Captain?
Sylvia?
That's right!
This is my class!
But where did everyone go?
Uh, the thing is...
Sylvia.
I need a favor.
Just in case we can't find Aine,
I brought you a substitute.
You mean me?
Kizuna-kun, that's not fair to Sylvia-chan!
Sylvia-chan, let's practice a little.
Yurishia-san?
I-I can't! It's too sudden!
I'll go look for Aine, then.
Bye!
Captain!
Come on in!
Now you can test-fire the Engineering
Division's latest railgun with no wait!
Kurumizawa.
Eros Overlord!
Kizuna!
My name is Kizuna Hida!
What's your problem?
That was a compliment.
It was not!
That aside, have you seen Aine?
Chidorigafuchi-san?
No, I haven't seen her come by.
I see.
Hey, while you're here...
Want to try our new railgun?
But I'm in a hurry...
Just come with me!
It's not going to just blow up, is it?
It's not. Don't underestimate
Momo Kurumizawa,
the Engineering Division's top student!
Yeah, got it.
I've got stuff to do,
so I'll only fire the one shot.
There's nothing difficult you need to do.
Good luck!
Put the target in the middle of the sights,
and flip the switch.
Flip the switch!
Shikina-san, what are you doing here?
Uh... Never mind.
Did you see Aine?
Haven't seen her.
Welcome back, Master.
Huh? You're the Masters...
Oh, it's you, Kizuna!
Did you come to see me in my maid outfit?
In this café,
you're the master of the Masters.
Order a lot, okay, Master?
This way.
What will you order, Master?
Let's see...
Wait, I'm not here for tea...
I'm looking for Aine.
We recommend this menu right here.
Moe Menu
Lap Pillow
Ear Picking
Instant Photo
Polaroid
Slap
Abuse
Hug
Patting
We also have a secret menu.
Would you like to take a look?
Uh-oh.
This maid café is dangerous!
You're leaving already?
I remembered something I have to do.
Here's your receipt, then.
That's expensive!
It includes the fee for the
information we gave you.
Thank you.
You didn't give me any information...
It's almost time for the concert to begin.
Where did she go, really?
If you want to kill me, then do it now!
General Grabel of the
6th Expeditionary Force.
You've gone from hero to traitor.
She decided on her own to make contact
with the Lemurian barbarians,
discovered Zeros and yet said nothing,
and tried to keep it for
herself, the traitor.
Zeros is in Lemuria?
Put together a fleet immediately!
Get Zeros if it means killing
every single Lemurian!
We've conquered more than enough of Lemuria!
What is the point of more murder?
There are civilians there, not just soldiers!
What of it?
Compared to what we seek,
their lives are meaningless.
I was originally a soldier of a country
that was conquered by Batlantis.
S-Stop it!
I can't allow you to invade...
...or oppress them for no reason...
I won't kill you.
I'll let you taste heaven without dying.
Wh-What is this?
Why?
I should only feel hate and pain,
so why do I feel so...?
How about this?
What's wrong?
Surrendering already?
Endure.
Aldea will come for you.
And then...
You think your friend will come for you?
Zelshione-sama!
Please, show me more love!
I'll do anything!
I'm your pet, after all!
Mind control?
Don't worry.
I'll make you my pet as well,
Bronze Beast.
First, you're going to
tell me where Zeros is.
We're going to Lemuria.
Our target is their mobile fortress.
Please wait a moment, Zelshione-sama.
You're...
Performing on the special stage on the ground
Amaterasu
Now, it's time for a special
academy festa performance!
They're usually a combat group,
but just for today...
...they're school idols!
No sign of Aine-san...
Let's go, Sylvia!
I-I'll do my best!
Give a big hand to the idols
of Ataraxia, Amaterasu!
It's started, huh?
Where did she go, really?
Hey, everybody!
Something was bothering her.
What's happening to her?
H-Hello!
Excuse me! I'm standing in for Aine-senpai!
Sylvia...
I'm Sylvia Silkcut!
Is she going to be okay?
Aine?
Kizuna...
Okay, everybody, here we go!
What's wrong? Why are you
sitting here by yourself?
I told you before, right?
That each time I do a Heart Hybrid,
some of my memories come back?
Yeah.
But maybe they might not be memories.
What do you mean?
I searched the database for the things I saw.
But they don't exist anywhere on Earth.
It's like another world...
Don't think too hard!
Take back hope!
Another... world...?
Aine?
I don't want to remember any more.
So I'm not going to do
any more Heart Hybrids.
But your Hybrid Count is getting low.
If you don't do it, your count
will drop to zero in the next fight—
No!
I'm scared!
I don't want to remember
any more strange things!
I feel like if I do,
I won't be the same person.
Aine.
Don't worry.
No matter what happens,
you are who you are.
Kizuna...
No matter what's in your past, I...
We won't change.
You'll always be one of us.
To me, you're no one but Aine Chidorigafuchi.
I'll shoot you through!
A burning hot gaze...
Get closer to me and make it
so you're only mine.
My heart's beating so fast.
Aine...
Don't hide them.
But I'm embarrassed...
Does it feel good?
D-Don't ask me.
You know it feels good...
No!
Love Gun High Power!
Aine!
Aine?
Seven loves shooting through the heart!
Captain, I did it!
What?
Kizuna!
Amaterasu needs to emergency scramble.
An enemy fleet has appeared.
The enemy fleet has come from
the Kanto area of Japan.
If we want to take back Tokyo,
we have to fight them at some point.
Let's go!
Look!
Someone's there!
Why is she there?
Mother...
It's been a long time, Kizuna.
Illustration: Yumi Nakata
That woman was always in front of me.
And so were her cold eyes that always
looked down on, mocked, and derided others.
Nayuta Hida, I will never forgive you.
Next time: Eve of the Decisive Battle -Install-
No matter what the cost,
no matter if it costs me my soul...